Guide to the New Jewish Agenda Records TAM.183
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Ithaca, New York Chapter Records, circa 1980-1992
  - "Chapter Newsletters", 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Records, circa 1980s, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Articles, 1982-1987 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, 1981-1987 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 18)